[You Have My Heart]
[Episode 5: Fall into This World]
My Lord.
Constable Chen.
My Lord,
You're awake.
Thanks to Lady Fufeng for saving you.
You must have encountered a possession demon.
According to ancient records,
This demon is formless.
It can possess a human's body and take his soul.
The victims
All took paper talismans.
You took quite a lot yesterday.
Didn't you say it is an echo demon?
Now you said it was a possession demon?
Perhaps there was no echo demon at all.
People here speak with an accent.
Possession demons. Possession demons.
It just turned into echo demons through word of mouth.
Everything in the world leaves a trace.
Whether it's an echo demon
Or a possession demon,
It was just a trick used by the killer
To cover up his crimes.
Young Magistrate.
You've investigated the echo demon for so long,
But you really don't believe it at all.
Whatever happens in Yin-Yang Crossing
Has nothing to do with me.
Once I finish investigating this case,
I will leave immediately.
Master.
You shouldn't have used so much spiritual power yesterday
To fight against Bai Han.
The seal of Kuquan Valley has been unstable recently.
You...
I must stop it.
This time,
It targets my tree heart.
But
That heart doesn't recognize you yet.
The spiritual spring is drying up day by day. As one falls, another rises.
How should we deal with it?
Just by fighting head-on,
I won't last long.
Now there is only one last way left.
Make its current master
Recognize me, obey me,
And truly become my man.
And then, I will let him
Offer himself,
Along with that heart, to me willingly.
There's corruption
Moving on Nanqiutou Road.
It's the Sun's Bakery.
[Sun's Bakery]
It's weird.
It's noon.
Why aren't they doing business?
I told you,
The mystery lies in this bakery shop.
What's that smell?
Is anyone inside?
-Open the door! -Is it on fire?
There is something wrong.
This smell is a bit strange.
It doesn't smell like normal firewood.
Something must have happened inside.
Don't touch it.
Your hand...
I'm fine.
The old man ran away.
Lady Fufeng,
It seems that the paper was just lit.
Did this paper catch fire on its own?
Why is there white smoke and black fire?
It's weird.
It's not spontaneous combustion.
It's purification.
The evil entity attached to the paper
Knew it couldn't hide anymore,
So it destroyed the evidence.
They are completely burned.
It's the corruption!
Gentlemen,
What are you doing in my shop?
Who are you?
I am the owner of this bakery shop.
This...
What happened to this cabinet?
I only closed my shop for a few days
And just got back.
Was I robbed?
Where is the one-eyed old man who was here before?
Sir,
Are you mistaken?
I am the only one who runs this shop.
I caught a cold a few days ago and took some time off.
I was just about to open.
You said you're the only one?
Yes.
Impossible.
A few days ago, we...
Hu.
Do you recognize this?
This...
No, I don't.
My Lady.
Speak your mind, Lord Bai.
I've checked the neighbors,
Household registers, and travel passes.
No one knows this one-eyed old man.
So?
Please enlighten me, My Lady.
You're truly adaptable, Lord Bai.
Then let me tell you.
The person you are looking for
Doesn't exist at all.
If so,
We can only collect clues from the people.
My Lady,
This is the notice I drafted.
I plan to post it tomorrow to offer a reward for clues.
Open it.
[Notice]
Stating the facts objectively
Won't help with getting clues.
It will only cause citywide panic.
But...
But if we hide it from the people,
They are more likely to be in danger.
Pen.
Here in Yin-Yang Crossing,
My name
Is more useful than your official seal.
[Liu Fufeng]
Just wear it.
It seems
You believe it a bit too.
My Lady.
You'd better apply some medicine to this burn.
It's just a scratch.
No need to worry, Lord Bai.
I'm better than someone overestimating himself
And nearly getting killed.
My Lady,
Why do you worry about me suddenly?
Because I want you to stay
And be my man.
My man ran into trouble while handling a case outside.
Wasn't it perfectly justified
For me to step in and solve it?
My Lady.
I... I am not your man.
Why are you still here?
I'm going to change and rest.
Thank you, My Lady.
I want you to be my man
And willingly offer your heart to me.
Master, this is the place.
This abandoned ancient well is
A rift we sealed years ago.
Someone broke a corner of the seal.
Fortunately,
The leak is small.
The corruption hasn't spread.
It was man-made.
The traces are fresh,
But they were highly skilled.
I can't find any clues.
I have sent people to reinforce the seal.
We've cleaned the escaping corruption around.
But
I am afraid that some people and spirits
Might have been affected by corruption.
We need to find them as soon as possible.
Otherwise,
Yin-Yang Crossing
Will really be in chaos.
Master.
The residual corruption
Disappears here.
Seems like it was stirred by something
And then covered up.
[Huichun Brothel]
She is fickle.
Originally, she wanted to kill me and cut out my heart.
But then, she asked me to investigate the case.
Now, she wanted me to stay
And become her man.
My Lady,
Why do you worry about me suddenly?
Because I want you to stay
And be my man.
She must have an ulterior motive.
My Lord.
Something happened at Huichun Brothel.
Should we go and take a look?
Huichun Brothel?
Master.
Though the state of death is terrifying,
The body hasn't been corrupted.
Let mortals handle
Mortal cases.
Someone died!
Someone died! Someone died!
Someone died! Let's go! Let's go!
Lord Bai,
Don't cause trouble at a time like this.
What do you mean?
Lady Fufeng is investigating the case.
If you rush in, offend Lady Fufeng,
And then alert that thing,
Who's going to take responsibility?
Watch your mouth.
My Lord,
We do trust you.
But Yin-Yang Crossing
Has never had so much trouble.
Fine.
Since Lady Fufeng is here,
I won't interfere.
Lord Bai is my man.
Let him in.
Go.
Lady Fufeng.
Rest assured, Lord Bai.
It hasn't been moved.
The people don't trust you,
But I do.
I believe
You can find out the truth.
So, I am here
Waiting for you.
The victim is female,
About 25 or 26 years old.
Her face was slashed multiple times,
But these wounds are not fatal.
There are signs of suspected poisoning.
This item is crucial evidence.
Thank you just now, Lady Fufeng.
Thank you?
I was just managing my territory
And protecting my man.
What do you need to thank me for?
Lady Fufeng,
I am an imperially appointed seventh-rank magistrate.
The court entitled me
And gave me my salary.
I'm not...
I'm not anyone else's man.
You say you're not my man
While using my power
Frequently.
Are you
Refuting me,
Or deceiving yourself?
Lady Fufeng.
If you want to take everything back,
I will have no complaints.
Lord Bai,
You've already tasted the power.
Why lie to yourself and say it's not sweet?
It's nothing but
Sugar-coated poison.
Every favor
Comes with a price.
Lady Fufeng, just tell me
Exactly what you want from me.
Lady Fufeng.
Lady Fufeng,
Please find out the truth
To redress the injustice for Wan.
Wan
Was a servant,
But she had a gentle temper.
Mingyuan has a bad temper,
But she wouldn't go as far as to kill someone.
There must be some misunderstanding.
Yes.
It must be a thief from outside.
What rumors have you heard in town?
Just tell us the rumors you've heard,
No matter how absurd they are.
Those are just gossip,
Which can't be taken seriously.
Gossip
Often hides some truths.
Tell me.
Some people said that
Wan was killed because of a love affair.
They said that Wan had been favored lately
And caught the eye of a frequent guest of Mingyuan's,
Mr. Du.
He promised that he would
Take Wan out of this misery.
When Mingyuan found out, she...
Others said
It was to silence her.
Over the years,
To keep her top position,
Mingyuan privately used some shady methods
To maintain her looks.
Wan accidentally caught her.
Wan was so honest
That she probably advised Mingyuan a bit.
Then, Mingyuan killed...
What else?
Is there anything related to Mingyuan herself?
Well.
Well, it's said that
As Mingyuan grows older,
Her appearance is not as good as it used to be.
She gets fewer guests.
Seeing Wan become more beautiful day by day,
Mingyuan was afraid Wan would take her place as the top courtesan.
So...
So, Mingyuan made up her mind
To ruin Wan's face
And kill her.
That's her. Search.
We should find Mingyuan, the suspect,
At any cost.
Yes.
Mingyuan, suspect in the Huichun Brothel murder case,
I am ordered to arrest you.
Escort her back to the county yamen
And hand her over to Lord Bai.
Let me go.
I didn't kill anyone.
I didn't.
Let me go.
Run! Run! Run!
I didn't kill anyone.
So handsome.
It's true, My Lord.
All the people on the street saw it.
Her face was like water,
And it instantly turned into mine.
Luckily, I'm a handsome man,
Which avoided a panic.
Otherwise, it would have caused trouble.
I think
You've lost your mind investigating the case.
I might have mistaken it.
But did all the people on the street
Get possessed?
Enough.
Open the door.
You know how to change your face.
Show Lord Bai.
She can change her face.
Aren't you capable?
Hurry up and show Lord Bai.
All right, that's enough.
Mingyuan.
Let me ask you.
Why did you kill the servant girl Wan
And disfigure her?
Confess everything.
Did she say anything?
Lord Bai,
Welcome to
The real Yin-Yang Crossing.